azoogleads.com 2012-05-04

# Epic Advertising. Performance Marketing, Simplified.

### Privacy Practices for Our Website

Epic Advertising ("us" or "we"). This Privacy Policy outlines our privacy practices on all our corporate properties (collectively, the "Websites"). You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (1) access or use the Websites; and/or (2) apply as a publisher ("Publisher") and/or advertiser ("Advertiser") (collectively, "Client(s)") services available through the Websites ("Services"). The Websites is not directed towards individual Internet consumers and does not seek any personally identifiable information from such consumers. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy, please do not use or access the Websites or apply for the Services. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at [help@epicadvertising.com](mailto:help@epicadvertising.com).

### Personally Identifiable Information:

We collect Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") from this Websites when you attempt to become a Client or otherwise choose to provide PII to us. PII is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity. This includes, but is not limited to: name, address, telephone number, mobile number and/or email address. For example, you may choose to send us PII about yourself in an email or by completing an online form on our Websites. Once collected, we will store your PII for a reasonable period of time for record keeping purposes. The information that we store is sometimes deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business.

###  Information Sharing: 

Epic Advertising will not sell, share or rent your PII to or with others. Your PII is not shared with any third parties, except: (a) where necessary to conduct business, such as invoicing a Client in connection with the Services or making payments to, or collecting money from, a Client; (b) in the case of a breach of any agreement between Client and Epic Advertising; (c) where required by law, or requested by a court of competent jurisdiction; (d) in the event of Epic Advertising’s bankruptcy, or if Epic Advertising is sold or acquired; or (e) where Epic Advertising determines, in its sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of Epic Advertising and/or a third party, or necessary to protect Epic Advertising from liability of any kind. 

###  Non-Personally Identifiable Information: 

We collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information ("Non-PII") from Websites visitors. Non-PII is information that cannot by itself be used to identify a particular person or entity, and may include your IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, Internet browsing and usage habits, Internet Service Provider, domain name, the time/date of your visit to our Websites, the referring URL and/or your computer's operating system. 

###  Cookies and Web Beacons:

We use "cookies" and web beacons to help us manage our Websites. Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. Web beacons (also known as "1X1 pixels" or "clear GIFs") are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. Web users have the option of blocking the use of cookies by changing a setting in their browser. Web users can check their browser supplier's website for details on how to do this. For more information about cookies and web beacons please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/>. 

###  Third Party Websites:

This Websites may contain links to and advertisements for websites operated by third parties whose privacy practices may differ from those of Epic Advertising. While we endeavor to associate only with reputable entities, Epic Advertising cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites. We encourage you to check the privacy policies of all websites that you visit. 

###  Minors:

This Websites is not intended for visitors that are under eighteen (18) years of age. Epic Advertising does not knowingly solicit or collect information from individuals under the age of thirteen (13). If we determine that we have inadvertently collected PII from someone under thirteen (13) years of age, we will take reasonable steps to purge this information from our database. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the Internet activities of their children.

###  Security:

All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. While we use SSL encryption to protect Sensitive Information online, we also do everything in our power to protect PII (including Sensitive Information) off-line. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect our end-users' PII, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Once we receive the transmission of your PII, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Access to this information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. All our end-users' PII is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example a customer service representative) are granted access to PII. Employees not adhering to our policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state law, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your PII. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures. 

###  Changes to this Privacy Policy & Notification of Changes:

Epic Advertising reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a clear and conspicuous notice on the Websites explaining that we are changing our Privacy Policy. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Websites. Please check the Websites periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Websites and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

###  Deleting your PII:

If you'd like us to delete any PII that you have provided to us on our Websites, please send your request to us at [help@epicadvertising.com](mailto:help@epicadvertising.com) and we will process your request, where possible and subject to the terms and conditions contained herein, within a reasonable period of time after receipt. 

###  Contacting the Websites:

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of Epic Advertising, please feel free to contact us at [help@epicadvertising.com](mailto:help@epicadvertising.com), or via postal mail at:

Epic Advertising.  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
512 7th Avenue, 12th Floor  
New York, NY 10018

Epic Advertising is a self-certified member of the U.S. Department of Commerce's EU Safe Harbor privacy program jointly established to comply with the European Commission's 1998 Directive on Data Protection. For more information about this privacy initiative, visit the Department of Commerce's website at <http://www.export.gov/safeHarbor/>.

EFFECTIVE DATE: February, 23, 2012
